Do you ever blend up a protein drink for breakfast, or grab a protein bar following an afternoon workout?
你是否会用搅拌机打一杯蛋白饮品当早餐，或是在下午健身后随手拿一根蛋白棒？
If so, you are likely among the millions of people in search of more protein-rich diets.
如果是这样，那么你很可能就是数以百万计追求蛋白质含量更高的饮食的人之一。
Protein-enriched products are found everywhere.
蛋白质强化产品随处可见。
But contrary to all the publicity claiming that everyone needs more protein, most Americans get twice as much as they need.
然而，与所有声称人人都需要更多蛋白质的宣传相反，大多数美国人摄入的蛋白质是其所需量的两倍。
Many of us living in the most developed countries are buying into a myth of protein deficiency created by food companies and self-identified health experts.
我们当中许多生活在最发达国家的人，正在轻信食品公司和自封的健康专家制造的蛋白质缺乏神话。
Global retail sales of protein supplement products reached an astonishing U.S. $18.9 billion in 2020.
2020年，全球蛋白质补充剂产品的零售额达到了惊人的189亿美元。
But are we really in need of more protein?
但我们真的需要更多蛋白质吗？
Most physicians in the U.S. have never actually examined a patient with protein deficiency because simply by eating an adequate number of daily calories we are also most likely getting enough protein.
美国的大多数医生其实从未诊察过蛋白质缺乏症患者，因为只要每天摄入足量的热量，我们极有可能也摄入了足够的蛋白质。
In fact, Americans currently consume almost twice the National Academy of Medicine’s recommended daily intake of protein, although the most desirable protein intake may vary depending on age and activity level.
事实上，美国人目前摄入的蛋白质几乎是美国国家医学院推荐的每日摄入量的两倍，不过，最理想的蛋白质摄入量可能因年龄和活动量而异。
For example, if you’re a dedicated athlete you might need to consume higher quantities of protein.
例如，如果你是一名全身心投入的运动员，可能就需要摄入更多蛋白质。
Generally, though, a 140-pound person should not exceed 120 grams of protein per day, particularly because a high-protein diet can strain kidney and liver function and increase risks of developing heart disease and cancer.
不过，一般来说，体重140磅的人每天的蛋白质摄入量不应超过120克，尤其是因为高蛋白饮食可能会使肾功能和肝功能负担过重，并增加患心脏病和癌症的风险。
While fats and sugar have taken a beating in turns for over a century, protein has managed to remain our red-hot favorite.
一个多世纪以来，脂肪和糖轮番遭受抨击，蛋白质却屹立不倒，始终是我们心中炙手可热的宠儿。
From the 1970s through the 1990s, protein products remained visible but moved back somewhat with the dietary spotlight firmly fixed on low-calorie, low-fat, sugar-free snack foods and beverages following the publication of studies linking sugar and saturated fat consumption to heart disease.
从20世纪70年代到90年代，蛋白质产品虽然仍在人们的视线之中，但多少有些退居其次：有研究把糖和饱和脂肪的摄入与心脏病联系起来，这些研究发表后，饮食领域的焦点便牢牢锁定在低热量、低脂、无糖的零食和饮料上。
Later research in 2003, however, suggested high-protein diets could aid in weight loss, and protein quickly regained its former nutrient-superstar status.
然而，2003年的后续研究表明，高蛋白饮食可能有助于减肥，蛋白质很快便重新获得了昔日营养素超级明星的地位。
Now most people living in high-income nations are consuming enough protein.
如今，生活在高收入国家的大多数人摄入的蛋白质都已足够。
When we replace meals with a protein bar or drink, we also risk missing out on the rich sources of antioxidants, vitamins and many other benefits of real food.
我们用蛋白棒或蛋白饮品代替正餐时，也就有可能错失真正的食物中丰富的抗氧化剂、维生素以及其他诸多益处。